<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: Scott Adams And His Voice	</title>
	<atom:link href="/old-blog/409/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/old-blog/409</link>
	<description>Amit Schreiber&#039;s Blog &#124; הבלוג של עמית שרייבר</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 04:56:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>
		By: Amit		</title>
		<link>/old-blog/409/comment-page-1#comment-838</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 04:56:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=409#comment-838</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In the field of exploring backdoors to the brain you&#039;re pretty much the most exploring person I know.
Maybe I&#039;ll give rhyming a shot :)

Thanks.]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the field of exploring backdoors to the brain you&#8217;re pretty much the most exploring person I know.<br />
Maybe I&#8217;ll give rhyming a shot :)</p>
<p>Thanks.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>
		By: Shai		</title>
		<link>/old-blog/409/comment-page-1#comment-837</link>

		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Shai]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2006 01:28:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=409#comment-837</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This is one of the most inspirational posts I&#039;ve ever heard. 
I also like to rhyme (write with rhymes, talk with rhymes, invent rhymes while talking, etc.) and I&#039;ve noticed time after time again that it leads to the formation of creative ideas, creative links, genuine inner self expression, and creativity in general. 
In my &quot;peaks&quot; I could even talk in a normal conversation using rhymes all the time, without losing it. It&#039;s like that when it kicks in it can go on an on.
(When I was a waiter there were certain shifts were I&#039;d talk to all my customers only in rhymes...)
I&#039;ve talked to a graduate student in Neurobioligy about Adams&#039; story, and she told me that singing and talking realted-brain-activity, are distinctly different, and I guess that rhyme is also &quot;something else&quot;.
This can also put the entire aspect of Prayer into some new comprehension.
I also identified with Adams when he said that he suddenly &quot;knew&quot; how to do it. That&#039;s my bit with rhyme-talking, I just &quot;know&quot; that if I won&#039;t doubt myself, and keep a positive approach, the correct rhyme will rise in the last minute, with a &quot;normal&quot; semantic validity, and (mostly) in the right contex. 
It also happens (to me), for example, with singing, dancing and courtship, things which I didn&#039;t &quot;know&quot; how to do as a teenager, yet found myself at different occasions doing them as if suddenly remembered how.
I usually attribute these &quot;new found abilites&quot; to my adventures in the the world of lucid dreaming where I continuously try to examine the limits of experince, ability, function, adventure, expression, and creativity, only to find myself later doing unexpected yet (sometimes...) beneficial acts in reality.
All this begs the question:
How much of our 95%+ non-functioning brain, is actually quite functioning, only waiting for us to find the &quot;backdoor&quot; (Do you hear this, Matrix fans ?) which will kick it back into action.

Well. Enough said....
Let&#039;s end with a rhyme by the English mystic  Aleister Crowley who was also an excellent rhymer:

We place no reliance
On virgin or pegion
Our method is science
Our aim is religion]]></description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is one of the most inspirational posts I&#8217;ve ever heard.<br />
I also like to rhyme (write with rhymes, talk with rhymes, invent rhymes while talking, etc.) and I&#8217;ve noticed time after time again that it leads to the formation of creative ideas, creative links, genuine inner self expression, and creativity in general.<br />
In my &#8220;peaks&#8221; I could even talk in a normal conversation using rhymes all the time, without losing it. It&#8217;s like that when it kicks in it can go on an on.<br />
(When I was a waiter there were certain shifts were I&#8217;d talk to all my customers only in rhymes&#8230;)<br />
I&#8217;ve talked to a graduate student in Neurobioligy about Adams&#8217; story, and she told me that singing and talking realted-brain-activity, are distinctly different, and I guess that rhyme is also &#8220;something else&#8221;.<br />
This can also put the entire aspect of Prayer into some new comprehension.<br />
I also identified with Adams when he said that he suddenly &#8220;knew&#8221; how to do it. That&#8217;s my bit with rhyme-talking, I just &#8220;know&#8221; that if I won&#8217;t doubt myself, and keep a positive approach, the correct rhyme will rise in the last minute, with a &#8220;normal&#8221; semantic validity, and (mostly) in the right contex.<br />
It also happens (to me), for example, with singing, dancing and courtship, things which I didn&#8217;t &#8220;know&#8221; how to do as a teenager, yet found myself at different occasions doing them as if suddenly remembered how.<br />
I usually attribute these &#8220;new found abilites&#8221; to my adventures in the the world of lucid dreaming where I continuously try to examine the limits of experince, ability, function, adventure, expression, and creativity, only to find myself later doing unexpected yet (sometimes&#8230;) beneficial acts in reality.<br />
All this begs the question:<br />
How much of our 95%+ non-functioning brain, is actually quite functioning, only waiting for us to find the &#8220;backdoor&#8221; (Do you hear this, Matrix fans ?) which will kick it back into action.</p>
<p>Well. Enough said&#8230;.<br />
Let&#8217;s end with a rhyme by the English mystic  Aleister Crowley who was also an excellent rhymer:</p>
<p>We place no reliance<br />
On virgin or pegion<br />
Our method is science<br />
Our aim is religion</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
