<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Fitness &#8211; Syntactically Correct</title>
	<atom:link href="/old-blog/category/fitness/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/old-blog/</link>
	<description>Amit Schreiber&#039;s Blog &#124; הבלוג של עמית שרייבר</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 09:28:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>10 Years Of Working Out</title>
		<link>/old-blog/3129</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit Schreiber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2014 17:06:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=3129</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This is the last time I&#8217;m going to mention my &#8220;gym anniversary.&#8221; After 10 years it&#8217;s safe to say that fitness (in some form or another) has become an integral part of my life. That&#8217;s not to say that I&#8217;m fit, but I do feel healthy and generally speaking I&#8217;m happy with my current look &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/old-blog/3129" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "10 Years Of Working Out"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is the last time I&#8217;m going to mention my &#8220;gym anniversary.&#8221; After 10 years it&#8217;s safe to say that fitness (in some form or another) has become an integral part of my life. That&#8217;s not to say that I&#8217;m fit, but I do feel healthy and generally speaking I&#8217;m happy with my current look and form. And that&#8217;s all I really ever wanted.</p>
<p>For now I&#8217;m going to keep the same routine I&#8217;ve had for the past couple of years &#8211; an 11km run, twice a week. Maybe I&#8217;ll change it sometime, but that won&#8217;t really matter, as long as I keep feeling well :)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>9 Years Of Working Out</title>
		<link>/old-blog/3056</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit Schreiber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2013 14:50:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=3056</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;m very busy so I&#8217;ll make it short :) This is the 9th anniversary of me going to the gym for the first time. Same as last year, I&#8217;m running 11+ km (in about one hour) twice a week with the addition of some simple workouts at home for the upper body. This has become &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/old-blog/3056" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "9 Years Of Working Out"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m very busy so I&#8217;ll make it short :)</p>
<p>This is the 9th anniversary of me going to the gym for the first time. Same as <a title="8 Years Of Working Out" href="/old-blog/2924">last year</a>, I&#8217;m running 11+ km (in about one hour) twice a week with the addition of some simple workouts at home for the upper body.</p>
<p>This has become part of my routine, so it&#8217;s not such a big deal. And that&#8217;s a good thing :)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happy Birthday To Me. I&#8217;m 36</title>
		<link>/old-blog/2995</link>
					<comments>/old-blog/2995#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit Schreiber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2013 07:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Playrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=2995</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[When I look at last year&#8217;s birthday post I realize how quickly time has passed. It&#8217;s like I wrote it yesterday. Compared to last year, 36 doesn&#8217;t come with thoughts about choices, but with a look to the future. It&#8217;s been two years now working on Playrock. We released as beta without advertising and are &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/old-blog/2995" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Happy Birthday To Me. I&#8217;m 36"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When I look at <a title="Happy Birthday To Me. I'm 35" href="/old-blog/2641">last year&#8217;s birthday post</a> I realize how quickly time has passed. It&#8217;s like I wrote it yesterday. Compared to last year, 36 doesn&#8217;t come with thoughts about choices, but with a look to the future.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s been two years now working on <a title="Playrock" href="/old-blog/category/playrock">Playrock</a>. We released as beta without advertising and are improving it all the time to make it better and more appealing to our users. I think Playrock is a great idea and we get very good responses from people that hear about it.</p>
<p>However, if Playrock doesn&#8217;t do well enough, I will be forced to look for a job. It&#8217;s not optimal, but not bad either &#8211; it will be a good time for me to explore overseas job opportunities, as I previously wanted to but never had the chance.</p>
<p>I traveled to see <a title="My 13th Prodigy Show - Warriors Dance Festival, Belgrade, Serbia" href="/old-blog/2885">The Prodigy for the 13th time in September</a> and had an amazing time thanks to some new friends in Belgrade, Serbia.</p>
<p>As for side projects: I haven&#8217;t had much time to work on those. My ideas list is growing and I might start working on one of them soon. As always, it will probably be a niche project that won&#8217;t appeal to many people, but it&#8217;ll be fun to code. I didn&#8217;t manage to find a designer for the website I built for my <a title="Idea: Online Will" href="/old-blog/1379">online will idea</a> that I already implemented, which is a shame because I was hoping to progress with that.</p>
<p>My workouts are <a title="8 Years Of Working Out" href="/old-blog/2924">still the same</a> and I&#8217;m relatively happy with my fitness and health.</p>
<p>So for the upcoming year I hope that either Playrock will be successful or for a different kind of adventure outside of Israel. Other than that&#8230; life is pretty good as is :)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/old-blog/2995/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>8 Years Of Working Out</title>
		<link>/old-blog/2924</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit Schreiber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 04 Oct 2012 17:30:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=2924</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Again I missed my gym anniversary by a day. My current workouts consist of running 11+ km (in about one hour) twice a week and some simple workouts at home for the upper body, which help me avoid some lower back pain I&#8217;ve suffered from lately. For some reason around this time of year running &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/old-blog/2924" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "8 Years Of Working Out"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Again I missed my gym anniversary by a day.</p>
<p>My current workouts consist of running 11+ km (in about one hour) twice a week and some simple workouts at home for the upper body, which help me avoid some lower back pain I&#8217;ve suffered from lately.</p>
<p>For some reason around this time of year running gets harder for me. I&#8217;m not sure if it&#8217;s weather-related or maybe DST-related, but it&#8217;s definitely there. Today&#8217;s run was relatively easy so that&#8217;s good.</p>
<p>I hope I can keep this routine for another year and maybe even go back to running three times a week.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Happy Birthday To Me. I&#8217;m 35</title>
		<link>/old-blog/2641</link>
					<comments>/old-blog/2641#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit Schreiber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 05:48:47 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Music]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Playrock]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Software]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=2641</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Wow. 35. This age comes with some serious what-am-I-doing-with-my-life kind of thoughts. Being unemployed, single and living with a cat at that age is hardly normative (at least in Israel) and despite being very content with the current situation it&#8217;s hard not to ponder other life choices. In any case, it&#8217;s time for the yearly &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/old-blog/2641" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Happy Birthday To Me. I&#8217;m 35"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Wow. 35. This age comes with some serious what-am-I-doing-with-my-life kind of thoughts. Being unemployed, single and living with a cat at that age is hardly normative (at least in Israel) and despite being very content with the current situation it&#8217;s hard not to ponder other life choices.</p>
<p>In any case, it&#8217;s time for the yearly look back:</p>
<p>A year ago I left my job to start a new venture with a friend. We since grew to a 3-person team and by now we have a very early version of our product, while we&#8217;re still tweaking the requirements for the first release. Hopefully in a few months we&#8217;ll have something to show for. This is probably the year in which we&#8217;ll know for sure whether this project is destined to take off or not.</p>
<p>Being unemployed (and having no income) for so long is my biggest worry for the upcoming year. I was very willing to spend some of my savings on this project, but I was hoping it will be in a better place by now. Other than that, I don&#8217;t think there&#8217;s a lot to say about entrepreneurship that hasn&#8217;t been said before. The joys and sorrows of this road are well documented in countless articles. I&#8217;m otherwise happy with my life, something I wished myself <a title="Happy Birthday To Me. I'm 34" href="/old-blog/2490">a year ago on my birthday post</a>.</p>
<p>Travelling: I was abroad twice &#8211; France/Germany and Switzerland. Both trips were great. Having already booked one trip for this year &#8211; to The Prodigy&#8217;s 3rd Warrior&#8217;s Dance Festival &#8211; I already made sure that I&#8217;ll keep &#8220;exploring the world&#8221; this year as well. Travelling has become one of my favorite things.</p>
<p>Side projects: I updated Dindy a few times in the past couple of weeks, hoping to address issues users have been experiencing for a while. I don&#8217;t plan to add any new features to Dindy &#8211; this was just to prevent it from rotting in the Android market. Unfortunately it hadn&#8217;t gained any new users for a long time now, yet it remains with a relatively high user score (4.2 out of 5.)</p>
<p>Another side project is my <a title="Idea: Online Will" href="/old-blog/1379">online will idea</a> from nearly 3 years ago. I already have an almost fully functional version of it running on Google App Engine, but there&#8217;s still a long way to go as it lacks visual design (if you&#8217;d like to help me with that &#8211; let me know) and there&#8217;s still quite a lot of code to write.</p>
<p>Workouts: Having suffered some injuries I&#8217;m working out (running) only twice a week now. I&#8217;m not happy about it, but I&#8217;m still in pretty good shape so it&#8217;s not that bad. I hope my injuries will subside and that I&#8217;ll be able to get back to my 3-workouts-a-week routine at some point.</p>
<p>That&#8217;s about it, I guess. I hope you&#8217;re happy too.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/old-blog/2641/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 Years Of Working Out</title>
		<link>/old-blog/2603</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit Schreiber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2011 04:06:52 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=2603</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s a little bit strange to write about the 7th anniversary of my first day at the gym after not actually doing any physical activity in the past 2 weeks due to what turned out to be just an infection (which I&#8217;m finally treating with some antibiotics.) That&#8217;s why it&#8217;s also not surprising that I &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/old-blog/2603" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "7 Years Of Working Out"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s a little bit strange to write about the 7th anniversary of my first day at the gym after not actually doing any physical activity in the past 2 weeks due to what turned out to be just an infection (which I&#8217;m finally treating with some antibiotics.) That&#8217;s why it&#8217;s also not surprising that I missed the actual date by a day. But I hope to get back to my running routine (3 times a week, 1 hour, ~11 km run) in a week or two considering that the pain is almost gone.</p>
<p>The big challenge over the past 8 months of workouts was running outside instead of in the gym. Running outside is considerably harder for me, especially when it&#8217;s hot, cold or raining. At some points during these months I&#8217;ve considered going back to the gym but eventually powered through. As winter is getting closer, I might reconsider.</p>
<p>So here&#8217;s to another workout year.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Taking The Week Off From Running Due To Pain</title>
		<link>/old-blog/2598</link>
					<comments>/old-blog/2598#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit Schreiber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2011 17:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=2598</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;ve been doing the same running routine for quite a while now &#8211; 3 times a week, 11.5km. Lately I&#8217;ve been experiencing some pelvic pain that refuses to go away. In 2 days I&#8217;m going to see an orthopedic doctor but for now, after reading online about some of the possible ailments (like Osteitis Pubis), &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/old-blog/2598" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Taking The Week Off From Running Due To Pain"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve been doing the same running routine for quite a while now &#8211; 3 times a week, 11.5km. Lately I&#8217;ve been experiencing some pelvic pain that refuses to go away. In 2 days I&#8217;m going to see an orthopedic doctor but for now, after reading online about some of the possible ailments (like <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Osteitis_pubis" title="Osteitis Pubis">Osteitis Pubis</a>), I&#8217;m taking this week off from running.</p>
<p>Every time I stop running because of pain I start fearing that following the rest period I won&#8217;t be able to get back to running. Even worse, I fear that I&#8217;ll regain the weight I&#8217;ve lost since I started working out nearly 7 years ago. These fears may be illogical, but I can&#8217;t help it.</p>
<p>Hopefully I&#8217;ll be better soon enough to go back to my running routine.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/old-blog/2598/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>6 Years Of Working Out</title>
		<link>/old-blog/2309</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit Schreiber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2010 05:53:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=2309</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s funny how this day turned out this year just as I returned from a trip and following almost two weeks that I haven&#8217;t been to the gym. Unlike years ago, I&#8217;m certain that I&#8217;ll be back to my workout routine (1 hour, 11 km run, 3 times a week) in a couple of days &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/old-blog/2309" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "6 Years Of Working Out"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s funny how this day turned out this year just as I returned from a trip and following almost two weeks that I haven&#8217;t been to the gym. Unlike years ago, I&#8217;m certain that I&#8217;ll be back to my workout routine (1 hour, 11 km run, 3 times a week) in a couple of days and I&#8217;m not worried about it at all. I&#8217;m more curious (and a little afraid) about how much weight I gained during these past two weeks. I hope it&#8217;s not a whole lot &#8211; that would freak me out :)</p>
<p>I guess this symbolizes the fact that I&#8217;ve made the workouts an integral part of my life. It&#8217;s no longer an effort, but a necessity.</p>
<p>By the way, I think I only missed one workout this year and made up for it later on. I have a rule that says &#8220;if I&#8217;m too sick to work out &#8211; I&#8217;m too sick to work.&#8221; There is no excuse for going to work while skipping a workout that is scheduled for the same day.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Knee Pains Update</title>
		<link>/old-blog/2169</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit Schreiber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2010 14:48:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=2169</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[OK, so I visited an orthopedic doctor and everything is fine. Apparently this isn&#8217;t an orthopedic issue at all &#8211; I presumably had a local sub-dermal cellulites infection very close to the knee area. It really hurt a few days ago, but now it seems to be passing. I should be back to regular workouts &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/old-blog/2169" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Knee Pains Update"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>OK, so I visited an orthopedic doctor and everything is fine. Apparently this isn&#8217;t an orthopedic issue at all &#8211; I presumably had a local sub-dermal cellulites infection very close to the knee area. It really hurt a few days ago, but now it seems to be passing.</p>
<p>I should be back to regular workouts in a few days. Yes!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Knee Pains</title>
		<link>/old-blog/2165</link>
					<comments>/old-blog/2165#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Amit Schreiber]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2010 08:45:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[English]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Fitness]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Personal]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/old-blog/?p=2165</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;m suffering from severe pain in my left knee. It started out as an innocent minor annoyance on Sunday morning. In the past such annoyances hadn&#8217;t stopped me from working out and this one didn&#8217;t either. I went on to run my usual 11km and when I was done I thought the two following days &#8230; <p class="link-more"><a href="/old-blog/2165" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Knee Pains"</span></a></p>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m suffering from severe pain in my left knee. It started out as an innocent minor annoyance on Sunday morning. In the past such annoyances hadn&#8217;t stopped me from working out and this one didn&#8217;t either. I went on to run my usual 11km and when I was done I thought the two following days until my next workout will suffice for my knee to recover, as it always did.</p>
<p>But I was wrong. My left knee is now swollen and inflamed and I&#8217;m having trouble walking, let alone running. It looks like I&#8217;m suffering from something called &#8220;runner&#8217;s knee&#8221; but I&#8217;m not sure. I&#8217;m worried about how long it will take before I&#8217;m back to running again. I&#8217;d hate to lose my aerobic fitness.</p>
<p>Anyway, it&#8217;s rest for my knee until further notice.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/old-blog/2165/feed</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>5</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
